BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 10) 6178/010
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Series XII: Industry Code #51, Information
  - Code no. 5756: Pacific Telephone and Telegraph Company, Los Angeles area and Southern Counties Area Plant, and Communications Workers of America, 1960-1966 (Box 19, Folder 5756)
  - Code no.5759: Pacific Telephone and Telegraph Company and Federation of Women Telephone Workers of Southern California, 1960- 1971 (Box 19, Folder 5759)
  - Code no.5763: Southern Bell Telephone and Telegraph Company and CWA, 1963-1966 (Box 19, Folder 5763)
  - Code no.5764: Southern New England Telephone Company and Connecticut Union of Telephone Workers, Inc., 1960-1966 (Box 19, Folder 5764)
  - Code no. 5765: Southwestern Bell Telephone Company and Communications Workers of America, 1960-1967 (Box 19, Folder 5765)
  - Code no. 5766:Southwestern Bell Telephone Company and Commuinications Workers of America, 1960-1968 (Box 19, Folder 5766)
  - Code no.5767: Southwestern Bell Telephone Company and CWA, 1960-1970 (Box 19, Folder 5767)
  - Code no. 5768: Southwestern Bell Telephone Company and Communications Workers of America, 1960-1968 (Box 19, Folder 5768)
  - Code no.5769: Southwestern States Telephone Company and CWA, 1960-1967 (Box 19, Folder 5769)
  - Code no.5770: West Coast Telephone Company and IBEW Local 77, 1965-1971 (Box 20, Folder 5770)
  - Code no.5776: RCA Communications, Inc. and American Communications Association, 1961-1971 (Box 20, Folder 5776)
  - Code no.5779: American Broadcasting Corporation and National Association of Broadcast Employees and Technicians, 1961- 1973 (Box 20, Folder 5779)
  - Code no.5782: National Broadcasting Corporation and National Association of Broadcast Employees and Technicians, 1961- 1970 (Box 20, Folder 5782)
  - Code no.5711: Chesapeake and Potomac Telephone Company and Maryland Telephone Union, Inc., 1963-1966 (Box 33, Folder 5711)
  - Code no.5712: Cincinnati and Suburban Bell Telephone Company and CWA, 1960-1974 (Box 33, Folder 5712)
  - Code no.5713: General Telephone Company of Michigan and IBEW Locals 818, 1172, 1174, 1177, 1190, 1410, 1962-1969 (Box 33, Folder 5713)
  - Code no.5720: General Telephone Company of Ohio and CWA, 1960-1969 (Box 33, Folder 5720)
  - Code no.5721: General Telephone Company of California and CWA, 1961-1970 (Box 33, Folder 5721)
  - Code no.5724: Illinois Bell Telephone Company and Telephone Commercial Employees' Union, 1960-1967 (Box 33, Folder 5724)
  - Code no.5725: Illinois Bell Telephone Company and Commercial Telephone Workers' Union, 1961-1970 (Box 33, Folder 5725)
  - Code no.5726: Illinois Bell Telephone Company and IBEW Local 811, 1961-1970 (Box 33, Folder 5726)
  - Code no.5727: Illinois Bell Telephone Company and IBEW Locals 134, 315, 336, 368, 371, 381, 399, 1960-1974 (Box 33, Folder 5727)
  - Code no.5731: Michigan Bell Telephone Company and CWA, 1960-1967 (Box 33, Folder 5731)
  - Code no.5733: Michigan Bell Telephone Company, Traffic Department and CWA, 1960-1967 (Box 33, Folder 5733)
  - Code no.5737: New England Telephone and Telegraph Company and The New England Federation of Telephone Accounting Workers, 1969-1966 (Box 33, Folder 5737)
  - Code no.5738: New Jersey Bell Telephone Company and CWA, 1964-1965 (Box 33, Folder 5738)
  - Code no.5739: New Jersey Bell Telephone Company and Telephone Workers Union Local 827, 1960-1965 (Box 33, Folder 5739)
  - Code no.5741: New Jersey Bell Telephone Company and CWA, 1961-1967 (Box 33, Folder 5741)
  - Code no.5744: New York Telephone Company and Telephone Commercial Union, 1960-1966 (Box 33, Folder 5744)
  - Code no.5746: New York Telephone Company and Union of Telephone Workers, 1963-1968 (Box 33, Folder 5746)
  - Code no.5760: Pacific Telephone and Telegraph Company and Organization of Plant Clerical and Office Forces of Northern California and Nevada, 1960-1963 (Box 34, Folder 5760)
  - Code no.5760: Bell Telephone Company of Nevada and Organization of Plant Clerical and Office Forces of Northern California and Nevada, 1960-1963 (Box 34, Folder 5760)
  - Code no.5761: Rochester Telephone Corporation and CWA Local 1170, 1961-1967 (Box 34, Folder 5761)
  - Code no.5763: Southern Bell Telephone and Telegraph Company and CWA, 1966-1974 (Box 34, Folder 5763)
  - Code no.5764: Southern New England Telephone Company and Connecticut Union of Telephone Workers, Inc., 1971-1974 (Box 34, Folder 5764)
  - Code no.5773: Wisconsin Telephone Company and CWA, 1960-1966 (Box 34, Folder 5773)
  - Code no.5774: Wisconsin Telephone Company and Traffic Department and CWA, 1960-1966 (Box 34, Folder 5774)
  - Code no.5781: American Broadcasting Corporation and American Federation of Musicians, 1959-1964 (Box 34, Folder 5781)
  - Code no.5781: Columbia Broadcasting System and American Federation of Musicians, 1959-1964 (Box 34, Folder 5781)
  - Code no.5781: National Broadcasting System and American Federation of Musicians, 1959-1964 (Box 34, Folder 5781)
  - Code no.5783: Diamond State Telephone Company and United Telephone Workers of Delaware, 1963-1971 (Box 34, Folder 5783)
  - Code no.5784: New England Telephone and Telegraph Company and International Brotherhood of Telephone Workers, 1964- 1974 (Box 34, Folder 5784)
  - Code no.5785: Network Television Broadcasting and American Federation of Television and Radio Artists, 1963-1969 (Box 34, Folder 5785)
  - Code no.5786: TV Recorded Commercials and American Federation of Television and Radio Artists, 1963-1969 (Box 34, Folder 5786)
  - Code no.5787: Transcriptions and American Federation of Television and Radio Artists, 1963-1973 (Box 34, Folder 5787)
  - Code no.5788: Commercial Radio and American Federation of Television and Radio Artists, 1963-1969 (Box 34, Folder 5788)
  - Code no.5790: National Code of Fair Practice and American Federation of Television and Radio Artists, 1963-1966 (Box 34, Folder 5790)
- Series XIII: Industry Code #52, Finance and Insurance
  - Code no.7403: Northwestern Mutual Life Insurance Company and Office and Professional Employees International Union Local 500, Chapter 35, 1960-1972 (Box 23, Folder 7403)
  - Code no.7412: Seattle-First National Bank and Employees' Association of Seattle-First National Bank, 1964-1970 (Box 36, Folder 7412)
- Series XIV: Industry Code #54, Professional, Scientific, and Technical Services
  - Code no.3787: Bell Telephone Laboratories, Inc. and CWA, 1964-1967 (Box 11, Folder 3787)
  - Code no.3673: ITT Federal Laboratories and IUE Local 400, 1959-1961 (Box 30, Folder 3673)
- Series XV: Industry Code #56, Administrative and Support and Waste Management and Remediation Services
  - Code no.6082: Chicago and Suburban Ash and Scavenger Association and Excavating, Grading, Asphalt, Private Scavengers and Automobile Salesroom Attendants Local 731, 1959-1971 (Box 23, Folder 6082)
- Series XVI: Code #62, Health Care and Social Assistance
  - Code no.7948: Association of Private Hospitals, Inc. and Hotel and Allied Service Employees Union Local 144, 1965-1972 (Box 36, Folder 7948)
  - Code no.7930: League of Voluntary Hospitals and Homes of New York and Drug and Hospital Union Local 1199, 1961-1974 (Box 36, Folder 7930)
- Series XVII: Code #72, Accommodation and Food Services
  - Code no.7104: Chicago Union Restaurant Employers Council and Chicago Area Local Joint Executive Board of the Hotel and Restaurant Employees International Union, 1960-1974 (Box 36, Folder 7104)
  - Code no.7100: Affiliated Restaurateurs, Inc. and Cafeteria Employees Union Local 302, 1959-1968 (Box 36, Folder 7100)
- Series XVIII: Code #81, Other Services (except Public Administration)
  - Code no.7709: Employer not listed and Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board, ACWA, 1960-1969 (Box 23, Folder 7709)